Mine is an Apatosaurus.
الخاص بي هو أباتوصور.
What about you?
ماذا عنك؟
Mine is a Triceratops.
ملكي هو Triceratops.
This one is hard to get.
من الصعب الحصول على هذا.
Stupid boys.
أولاد أغبياء.
Dinosaurs are so ugly.
الديناصورات قبيحة جدًا.
What's cute about them?
ما هو اللطيف فيهم؟
Lu Junxi!
لو جونكسي!
Your mom is here to take you home.
والدتك هنا لتأخذك إلى المنزل.
Okay, coming!
حسنا، قادم!
You look really happy.
أنت تبدو سعيدًا حقًا.
Bye, Junxi.
وداعا جونشي.
Bye, Junxi's mom.
وداعا أم جونكسي.
Bye, Xiaoyang.
وداعا شياويانغ.
Bye, Tuo.
وداعا، توو.
What did you play today?
ماذا لعبت اليوم؟
The slide.
الشريحة.
The slide, huh?
الشريحة، هاه؟
Was it fun?
هل كان ممتعا؟
Yeah, it was.
نعم كان كذلك.
Tuo.
هذا كل شيء.
Come to my house for dinner.
تعال إلى منزلي لتناول العشاء.
Come on, let's go.
هيا لنذهب.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
[Episode 5: Liking and Love Both Happen in an Instant]
[الحلقة 5: الإعجاب والحب يحدثان في لحظة]
[Secret Lover]
[الحبيب السري]
[Stellar Studio: Off-Campus Internship Notice for Game Design Students]
[Stellar Studio: إشعار بالتدريب خارج الحرم الجامعي لطلاب تصميم الألعاب]
I wonder if I'll get the internship.
أتساءل عما إذا كنت سأحصل على التدريب.
Don't worry,
لا تقلق،
you're the best.
أنت الأفضل.
By the way, why have you been...
بالمناسبة، لماذا كنت...؟
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
I got some sand in my eye.
لقد دخلت بعض الرمال في عيني.
Let me see.
دعني أرى.
Is that better?
هل هذا افضل؟
It's been over a week since I sent my work to Stellar Studio,
لقد مر أكثر من أسبوع منذ أن أرسلت عملي إلى Stellar Studio،
but there's still no response.
ولكن لا يوجد رد حتى الآن.
I guess there's no hope.
أعتقد أنه لا يوجد أمل.
Tuo, what about you?
توو، ماذا عنك؟
I'm still waiting for
مازلت انتظر
a reply from Zhan Wensen Architect Studio.
رد من استوديو Zhan Wensen المعماري.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
You've won the Book Award three times in a row,
لقد فزت بجائزة الكتاب ثلاث مرات متتالية،
and your works have won prizes.
وقد فازت أعمالك بجوائز.
You'll definitely get in.
سوف تحصل على دخول بالتأكيد.
Same for you, Xiaoyang.
نفس الشيء بالنسبة لك، شياويانغ.
You're strong in both art and programming, so you'll surely get in.
أنت قوي في كل من الفن والبرمجة، لذلك سوف تنجح بالتأكيد.
Same for me.
نفس الشيء بالنسبة لي.
I'm probably the least likely to make it.
أنا على الأرجح الأقل احتمالا لتحقيق ذلك.
Although I can do programming,
على الرغم من أنني أستطيع القيام بالبرمجة،
I'm just average at it.
أنا فقط متوسط في ذلك.
Be more confident.
كن أكثر ثقة.
You're the one debugging the games,
أنت الشخص الذي يقوم بتصحيح أخطاء الألعاب،
so the characters can transform from stiff puppets
حتى تتمكن الشخصيات من التحول من الدمى الجامدة
into something as smooth as Spider-Man.
إلى شيء سلس مثل سبايدر مان.
You've got this.
لقد حصلت على هذا.
Yeah. You can do it.
نعم، يمكنك فعل ذلك.
You again?
انت مرة اخرى؟
How do you know we are here?
كيف تعرف أننا هنا؟
In my world,
في عالمي،
you are the guiding force that shows me the way forward.
أنت القوة المرشدة التي تظهر لي الطريق إلى الأمام.
If we can't be friends,
إذا لم نستطع أن نكون أصدقاء،
can we at least be lunch buddies?
هل يمكننا على الأقل أن نكون أصدقاء الغداء؟
I've been eating alone
لقد كنت أتناول الطعام بمفردي
since school started.
منذ بدء المدرسة.
So you won't bother Junxi anymore?
إذن فلن تزعج جونكسي بعد الآن؟
I won't, I swear.
لن أفعل ذلك، أقسم بذلك.
Just a friend.
مجرد صديق.
Please!
لو سمحت!
Let's eat together.
دعونا نأكل معا.
Let's dig in!
دعونا نبدأ!
Class's finally over.
لقد انتهى الدرس أخيرا.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Bye, couple.
وداعا أيها الزوجان.
I'll go with you.
سأذهب معك.
Sorry.
آسف.
I forgot I promised my friends to play Takara today,
لقد نسيت أنني وعدت أصدقائي باللعب بالتاكارا اليوم،
so I can't go home with you.
لذلك لا أستطيع العودة إلى المنزل معك.
I'll call you when I'm done.
سأتصل بك عندما أنتهي.
Okay.
تمام.
Bye.
الوداع.
Is gaming more important than dating?
هل الألعاب أكثر أهمية من المواعدة؟
I almost want to cry for Tuo.
أنا أريد أن أبكي من أجل توو.
If I don't make this excuse,
إذا لم أقدم هذا العذر،
Tuo will definitely find out.
سوف تكتشف ذلك بالتأكيد.
Find out what?
اكتشف ماذا؟
Tuo's birthday is coming up,
عيد ميلاد توو قادم،
and I want to discuss with you
وأريد أن أناقش معك
about how to plan for it.
حول كيفية التخطيط لذلك.
I thought you two would want to celebrate alone this year.
اعتقدت أنكما قد ترغبان في الاحتفال بمفردكما هذا العام.
No way.
مستحيل.
We're a trio.
نحن ثلاثي.
Of course we'll celebrate together.
بالطبع سوف نحتفل معًا.
Not abandoning friends for love, I'll give you credit for that.
لا أتخلى عن الأصدقاء من أجل الحب، وسأمنحك الفضل في ذلك.
So what do you want to give him?
إذن ماذا تريد أن تعطيه؟
That's exactly what's bothering me.
هذا بالضبط ما يزعجني.
He always says there's nothing he wants.
يقول دائمًا أنه لا يريد شيئًا.
That's easy.
هذا سهل.
Just tie a bow around your neck,
فقط قم بربط القوس حول رقبتك،
and you'll be his best birthday present.
وستكونين أفضل هدية عيد ميلاد له.
I'm being serious.
أنا جاد.
Are you actually considering it?
هل تفكر في ذلك فعلا؟
Alright, I'll stop teasing you.
حسنًا، سأتوقف عن مضايقتك.
Let's just go shopping
دعنا نذهب للتسوق فقط
and look for inspiration.
وابحث عن الإلهام.
Sure, I was thinking the same.
بالتأكيد، كنت أفكر نفس الشيء.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Or maybe
أو ربما
the bow should be tied somewhere else?
هل ينبغي ربط القوس في مكان آخر؟
Stop teasing me.
توقف عن مضايقتي.
[Junxi]
[جونشي]
[Mr. Ex, it's time to pay me back.]
[السيد السابق، لقد حان الوقت لتسديد ديني.]
Hey.
يا.
The general studies group project
مشروع مجموعة الدراسات العامة
is getting harder and harder.
يصبح الأمر أصعب وأصعب.
Don't try to push it on me.
لا تحاول فرض ذلك علي.
Do it on your own.
افعل ذلك بنفسك.
I was hoping you'd help me with mine too.
كنت آمل أن تساعدني في مشكلتي أيضًا.
I'll think about it.
سأفكر في الأمر.
I have things to do. I'm off.
لدي أشياء لأفعلها. سأذهب.
Why does he keep running off lately?
لماذا يستمر في الهروب في الآونة الأخيرة؟
I have no idea.
ليس لدي أي فكرة.
I smell cheating.
أنا أشم رائحة الغش.
It's you again.
أنت مرة أخرى.
Can you not scare us every time?
هل يمكنك أن لا تخيفنا في كل مرة؟
That's what you get for never inviting me to eat with you.
هذا ما تحصل عليه لعدم دعوتي أبدًا لتناول الطعام معك.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
Tuo's birthday is coming up.
عيد ميلاد توو قادم.
Let's go pick out a gift for him later.
دعونا نذهب لاختيار هدية له في وقت لاحق.
-I'll go, too! -Okay.
-سأذهب أيضًا! -حسنًا.
You really like following us.
إنك تحب متابعتنا حقًا.
I have
أملك
a pocket list of fancy gift shops on my phone.
قائمة جيب لمتاجر الهدايا الفاخرة على هاتفي.
[Selected Gift Shops]
[متاجر الهدايا المختارة]
Come on, let's go.
هيا لنذهب.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Hurry up. Chop chop.
اسرع. قطع قطع.
Which one shall we go to?
إلى أي واحد نذهب؟
Let me remind you.
دعني أذكرك.
Men are the kind of creatures
الرجال هم نوع من المخلوقات
who stop cherishing something once they have it.
الذين يتوقفون عن تقدير الشيء بمجرد حصولهم عليه.
Han Tuo's recent disappearing act is definitely suspicious.
من المؤكد أن اختفاء هان توه في الآونة الأخيرة أمر مثير للريبة.
He must be hiding something.
لابد أنه يخفي شيئاً ما.
[Jiamei Hotel]
[فندق جيامي]
Tuo!
هذا كل شيء!
Psychologist Barbara Fredrickson
عالمة النفس باربرا فريدريكسون
presented her research results on love
قدمت نتائج بحثها عن الحب
in her 2013 book "Love 2.0,"
في كتابها الصادر عام 2013 بعنوان "الحب 2.0"،
advocating that we rethink the definition of love.
الدعوة إلى إعادة التفكير في تعريف الحب.
What on earth have you been so busy with lately?
ما الذي كنت مشغولاً به كثيرًا في الآونة الأخيرة؟
Yawning in class, ditching gatherings,
التثاؤب في الفصل، والتخلي عن التجمعات،
and constantly canceling dates with Junxi.
وإلغاء المواعيد مع جونكسي باستمرار.
Enduring, unchanging love doesn't exist.
الحب الدائم الذي لا يتغير غير موجود.
The nature of love is fleeting,
طبيعة الحب عابرة،
fragmented, and discontinuous.
مجزأة وغير متصلة.
That guy over there is so handsome.
هذا الرجل هناك وسيم جداً.
Are you feeling better?
هل تشعر بتحسن؟
That's ridiculous.
هذا سخيف.
The one next to him.
الذي بجانبه.
Why is he with...
لماذا هو مع...
Junxi.
جونكسي.
Love is actually a tiny momentary feeling,
الحب في الواقع هو شعور صغير مؤقت،
even more fleeting than we imagine.
أكثر عابرًا مما نتصور.
The moments when people truly feel love
اللحظات التي يشعر فيها الناس بالحب الحقيقي
actually last only a few seconds.
في الواقع تستمر لبضع ثوان فقط.
This theory is too biased.
هذه النظرية متحيزة للغاية.
If eternal love doesn't exist,
إذا لم يكن هناك حب أبدي،
why is "Romeo and Juliet" so popular?
لماذا يعتبر "روميو وجولييت" مشهورًا جدًا؟
That's just a play.
إنها مجرد مسرحية.
Isn't its popularity proof
أليس هذا دليلا على شعبيته؟
that most people desperately want to believe love is eternal?
هل يريد أغلب الناس بشدة أن يصدقوا أن الحب أبدي؟
This is just your personal theory, Professor,
هذه مجرد نظريتك الشخصية يا أستاذ.
not necessarily the fact.
ليس بالضرورة الحقيقة.
The research you just mentioned
البحث الذي ذكرته للتو
is over a decade old,
يبلغ عمره أكثر من عقد من الزمان،
and the findings may not be accurate.
وقد لا تكون النتائج دقيقة.
He's going too far. What is he doing?
لقد تجاوز الحد. ماذا يفعل؟
Challenging the teacher.
تحدي المعلم.
Yeah, he's really going overboard.
نعم، إنه يبالغ حقًا.
What is he doing?
ماذا يفعل؟
[What are you doing after dinner? Are you coming tonight? Where are you?]
ماذا تفعل بعد العشاء؟ هل ستأتي الليلة؟ أين أنت؟
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
The professor was just introducing a psychology case study.
كان الأستاذ يقدم للتو دراسة حالة في علم النفس.
Why were you upset about that?
لماذا كنت منزعجا من ذلك؟
I was just having an academic discussion with the professor.
كنت فقط أجري مناقشة أكاديمية مع الأستاذ.
Can I borrow your notes again?
هل يمكنني استعارة ملاحظاتك مرة أخرى؟
You take really good notes.
لقد أخذت ملاحظات جيدة حقًا.
You didn't take notes again?
لم تأخذ ملاحظات مرة أخرى؟
Please, this is the last time.
من فضلك هذه المرة الأخيرة.
Last time, okay?
المرة الأخيرة، حسناً؟
Don't be jealous,
لا تغار
Tuo.
هذا كل شيء.
Such a jealous guy.
مثل هذا الرجل الغيور.
No,
لا،
more like a total jealousy machine.
أشبه بآلة الغيرة الكاملة.
[All-Gender Restroom]
[حمام لجميع الجنسين]
How many times have I reminded you
كم مرة ذكّرتك
not to let girls get too close to you?
لا تسمح للفتيات بالاقتراب منك كثيرًا؟
Did you hear me?
هل سمعتني؟
She has a boyfriend.
لديها صديق.
She's just someone from my gen-ed class, asking to borrow my notes.
إنها مجرد شخص من صفي التعليمي العام، يطلب استعارة ملاحظاتي.
Even if she has a boyfriend,
حتى لو كان لديها صديق،
you should still keep your distance.
لا يزال يتعين عليك الحفاظ على المسافة الخاصة بك.
It's not like it's contagious.
إنه ليس معديا.
Come over to my place today.
تعال إلى مكاني اليوم.
My bad.
خطئي.
What?
ماذا؟
I mean I'm sorry,
أعني أنني آسف،
I was too rough just now.
لقد كنت قاسياً جداً الآن.
Well, I didn't say no.
حسنًا، لم أقل لا.
It's been a while since we...
لقد مر وقت طويل منذ أن...
Still laughing.
لا زال يضحك.
What's so funny?
ما المضحك في هذا؟
This is all your fault.
كل هذا خطؤك .
Does your back hurt?
هل يؤلمك ظهرك؟
I'll be gentler next time.
سأكون أكثر لطفًا في المرة القادمة.
Let me give you a massage.
دعني أعطيك تدليكًا.
Love is definitely not just a momentary feeling.
الحب بالتأكيد ليس مجرد شعور مؤقت.
Get some sleep.
احصل على بعض النوم.
I'll be right back.
سأعود حالا.
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
It's weird.
إنه أمر غريب.
What's weird?
ما هو الغريب؟
It's really weird.
إنه أمر غريب حقا.
Don't listen to her nonsense.
لا تستمع إلى هراءها.
The report is due tomorrow. Hurry up and write it.
موعد تسليم التقرير غدًا. سارع بكتابته.
What's more important, the report or your boyfriend?
ما هو الأهم التقرير أم صديقك؟
Your boyfriend, of course!
صديقك بالطبع!
Think about it.
فكر في الأمر.
Has Han Tuo been acting
هل كان هان توه يمثل؟
strangely lately,
غريبًا في الآونة الأخيرة،
like,
يحب،
disappearing as soon as he gets a message?
يختفي بمجرد حصوله على رسالة؟
I need to go now.
أحتاج أن أذهب الآن.
Get some sleep.
احصل على بعض النوم.
I'll be right back.
سأعود حالا.
Or
أو
suddenly being protective of his phone, not letting you see it and stuff?
فجأة أصبح يحمي هاتفه، ولا يسمح لك برؤيته وما إلى ذلك؟
Don't overthink it.
لا تفكر كثيرا في الأمر.
Tuo wouldn't do that.
توو لن يفعل ذلك.
I'm serious.
أنا جادة.
I've been there.
لقد كنت هناك.
Remember,
يتذكر،
the first line in the players' handbook is
السطر الأول في دليل اللاعبين هو
"I'm a bit busy right now,
"أنا مشغول قليلاً الآن،
find something to do on your own."
ابحث عن شيء تفعله بنفسك."
Men's words are nothing but lies.
كلام الرجال ليس إلا كذبا.
I'm so tired of that mouth of yours.
لقد سئمت من هذا الفم الخاص بك.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Okay.
تمام.
I'll come get it in a bit. Thanks.
سآتي لأخذه بعد قليل. شكرًا.
Tuo's gift is ready.
هدية توو جاهزة.
It was the store, telling us to go pick it up.
لقد كان المتجر يطلب منا أن نذهب لاستلامه.
Great!
عظيم!
Let's go together!
دعنا نذهب معا!
Grab your bag, come on.
خذ حقيبتك، هيا.
Hurry up!
عجلوا!
Where's your bag?
أين حقيبتك؟
And yours?
وما تملكه؟
-Let's go. Come on. Hurry up. -Wait.
-هيا بنا. هيا. أسرع. -انتظر.
Am I playing the prophet today
هل ألعب دور النبي اليوم؟
or being a jinx?
أو أنك نحس؟
And she's paying him.
وهي تدفع له.
It's not prostitution, is it...
إنها ليست دعارة، أليس كذلك؟
Let's get the facts first.
دعونا نحصل على الحقائق أولاً.
That's right. Why should the wife give way to the mistress?
صحيح. لماذا تُفسح الزوجة المجال لسيدتها؟
We should stand our ground and teach them a lesson.
ينبغي علينا أن نقف على أرضنا ونعلمهم درسًا.
He Youmei, don't make things worse, okay?
هي يو مي، لا تجعل الأمور أسوأ، حسنًا؟
Lin Xiaoyang.
لين شياويانغ.
Lu Junxi. Long time no see.
لو جونشي. وقت طويل لا رؤية.
Who is she?
من هي؟
Our high school classmate,
زميلنا في المدرسة الثانوية،
Tuo's ex-girlfriend.
صديقة توو السابقة.
Junxi!
جونشي!
What's going on with them?
ماذا يحدث معهم؟
He ran away,
لقد هرب
then he chased after him,
ثم طارده
and then...
وثم...
He caught him.
لقد أمسك به.
That's so lame.
هذا سخيف جدًا.
Seriously,
بجد،
he could've at least made it around the corner before getting caught.
كان بإمكانه على الأقل أن يصل إلى الزاوية قبل أن يتم القبض عليه.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
Great minds think alike,
العقول العظيمة تفكر على نحو مماثل،
Sis, I'm He Youmei. And you?
أختي، أنا هي يومي. وأنتِ؟
Tian Xinhui.
تيان شينهوي.
Oh no, weirdo meets weirdo.
أوه لا، الغريب يلتقي بالغريب.
I'm having a headache.
أنا أعاني من صداع.
Look.
ينظر.
So cute.
ظريف جدًا.
If you still have feelings for Tian Xinhui,
إذا كان لا يزال لديك مشاعر تجاه تيان شين هوي،
you can tell me.
يمكنك أن تخبرني.
It's not what you think between me and Tian Xinhui.
إنه ليس ما تعتقد بيني وبين تيان شين هوي.
You came out of the hotel together, how else am I supposed to think?
لقد خرجتما من الفندق معًا، كيف من المفترض أن أفكر بطريقة أخرى؟
I was working there.
كنت أعمل هناك.
Working?
عمل؟
Come to a place with me.
تعال إلى مكان معي.
[Cool PC Digital Syntrend Store]
[متجر Cool PC Digital Syntrend]
Tuo.
هذا كل شيء.
The NJ-66 you ordered hasn't arrived yet,
لم تصل الطائرة NJ-66 التي طلبتها بعد،
but the keyboard is here.
ولكن لوحة المفاتيح موجودة هنا.
This is a free gift.
هذه هدية مجانية.
I'll go get the mouse for you.
سأذهب لأحضر لك الفأر.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
NJ-66?
نيوجيرسي-66؟
Why are you buying a gaming PC?
لماذا تشتري جهاز كمبيوتر للألعاب؟
You don't even play games.
أنت لا تلعب حتى الألعاب.
It's for you.
إنه لك.
This way, you can play games at my place
بهذه الطريقة، يمكنك لعب الألعاب في مكاني
without having to running back and forth,
دون الحاجة إلى الجري ذهابًا وإيابًا،
and you can play while keeping me company.
ويمكنك اللعب مع إبقاءني في صحبتك.
But the NJ-66 alone costs 70,000 to 80,000.
لكن سعر NJ-66 وحده يتراوح بين 70 ألفًا و80 ألفًا.
Tian Xinhui works at an investigation agency.
تيان شين هوي يعمل في وكالة تحقيق.
She asked me to accompany her to the hotel to collect evidence.
طلبت مني أن أرافقها إلى الفندق لجمع الأدلة.
[Jiamei Hotel]
[فندق جيامي]
Tuo.
هذا كل شيء.
Let me tell you.
دعني أخبرك.
We'll first meet with a photographer,
سنلتقي أولاً مع المصور،
and then we'll go to their room
وبعد ذلك سنذهب إلى غرفتهم
and block them.
وحجبهم.
The hourly wage is paid daily.
يتم دفع الأجر بالساعة يوميًا.
The salary is very good.
الراتب جيد جداً
You could have told me first.
كان بإمكانك أن تخبرني أولاً.
If I had told you first, it wouldn't have been a surprise.
لو قلت لك أولاً، لن تكون مفاجأة.
I'm sorry for misunderstanding you.
أنا آسف على سوء فهمك.
It's my fault for not explaining clearly,
إنه خطئي لأنني لم أشرح بوضوح،
causing you to misunderstand.
مما يسبب لك سوء الفهم.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
I've also prepared a small gift for you.
لقد أعددت لك هدية صغيرة أيضًا.
I drew it myself.
لقد رسمتها بنفسي.
If you don't like it
إذا لم يعجبك ذلك
or think it's too ordinary,
أو أعتقد أنها عادية جدًا،
you can give it back to me.
يمكنك إعادته لي.
I love it so much.
انا احبه كثيرا.
You must have noticed that my phone case was broken,
يجب أن تكون قد لاحظت أن غطاء هاتفي كان مكسورًا،
so you prepared this for me, right?
إذن لقد أعددت هذا لي، أليس كذلك؟
Your birthday is coming up,
عيد ميلادك قادم،
and I didn't know what to get you.
ولم أعرف ماذا أحضر لك.
Compared to the gift you gave me,
مقارنة بالهدية التي قدمتها لي،
this is really nothing special.
هذا ليس شيئا خاصا حقا.
Who says that?
من يقول ذلك؟
You always give me exactly what I need.
أنت تعطيني دائمًا ما أحتاجه بالضبط.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Hi, Xiaoyang.
مرحبًا شياويانغ.
Are you guys done?
هل إنتهيتم؟
Tian Xinhui wants to throw an early birthday party for Tuo.
يريد تيان شين هوي إقامة حفلة عيد ميلاد مبكرة لتو.
You must come,
يجب عليك أن تأتي
or I'll
أو سأفعل
kidnap Xiaoyang and never give her back to you.
اختطاف شياويانغ وعدم إعادتها إليك أبدًا.
Right, we'll kidnap Xiaoyang.
حسنًا، سوف نختطف شياويانغ.
Fine by me.
جيد بالنسبة لي.
Cut it out.
اقطعها.
Okay, I'll send you the location.
حسنًا، سأرسل لك الموقع.
Be there or be square.
كن هناك أو كن مربعا.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
[Matsutaka]
[ماتسوتاكا]
Cheers!
هتافات!
Buying a gift turned into a whole drama.
لقد تحول شراء هدية إلى دراما كاملة.
No, more like a drama for us.
لا، بل هو بمثابة دراما بالنسبة لنا.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
It was just buying a computer.
كان مجرد شراء جهاز كمبيوتر.
Why go work at an investigation agency?
لماذا العمل في وكالة تحقيقات؟
If you're short on money, we could all chip in.
إذا كنت تعاني من نقص المال، فيمكننا جميعًا المساهمة.
It only means something if I earn it myself.
لا يعني هذا شيئًا إلا إذا كسبته بنفسي.
Let me see it.
دعني أرى ذلك.
No way.
مستحيل.
So stingy.
بخيل جداً.
Why does it have a dinosaur pattern?
لماذا يوجد نمط الديناصور؟
Because Tuo...
لأن...
It's a secret.
إنه سر.
Forget it then. We have our secrets too.
انسَ الأمر إذن، لدينا أسرارنا أيضًا.
But we don't.
ولكننا لا نفعل ذلك.
[Matsutaka]
[ماتسوتاكا]
Tuo, happy birthday!
هذا صحيح، عيد ميلاد سعيد!
Cheers!
هتافات!
We've toasted so many times already.
لقد احتفلنا عدة مرات بالفعل.
I don't care.
لا أهتم.
Cheers!
هتافات!
The one I used to like
الذي كنت أحبه
was you.
هل كنت انت؟
Are you sure Junxi will take this route?
هل أنت متأكد أن جونكسي سوف يتخذ هذا الطريق؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
This is the only route back from the welfare store.
هذا هو الطريق الوحيد للعودة من متجر الرعاية الاجتماعية.
Have you decided how to confess?
هل قررت كيفية الاعتراف؟
I'll stop him
سأوقفه
and invite him to the gaming expo.
ودعوته إلى معرض الألعاب.
I'll find a chance to confess by then.
سأجد فرصة للاعتراف بحلول ذلك الوقت.
He's coming. He's coming.
إنه قادم.إنه قادم.
If you take another step,
إذا اتخذت خطوة أخرى،
I'll lose my chance at love.
سأفقد فرصتي في الحب.
In high school,
في المدرسة الثانوية،
you confessed to me.
لقد اعترفت لي.
It was all fake.
لقد كان كل ذلك مزيفًا.
Tian Xinhui, shut up.
تيان شينهوي، اصمت.
Why are you being so harsh?
لماذا أنت قاسي هكذا؟
What's with that attitude?
ما الأمر مع هذا الموقف؟
You owe me this.
أنت مدين لي بهذا.
I wanted to confess to Junxi,
أردت أن أعترف لجونكسي،
but you got in my way
ولكنك وقفت في طريقي
and said you wanted to date me.
وقلت أنك تريد مواعدتي.
You didn't even like me!
أنت لم تحبني حتى!
You just didn't want
أنت فقط لم تريد
me to pursue Junxi.
لي لمتابعة Junxi.
You jerk!
يا لك من أحمق!
Don't tell me
لا تخبرني
all of Tuo's ex-girlfriends
جميع صديقات توو السابقات
liked Junxi first.
أحببت جونكسي أولاً.
Tuo.
هذا كل شيء.
Is that true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
Tuo!
هذا كل شيء!
[Matsutaka]
[ماتسوتاكا]
Han Tuo!
هان تو!
[In the Next Episode]
[في الحلقة القادمة]
Tuo also received an interview notice from Zhan Wensen.
وتلقى توو أيضًا إشعارًا بإجراء مقابلة من تشان وينسن.
Looking forward to your joining.
نتطلع إلى انضمامك.
You're up early.
لقد استيقظت مبكرا.
Han Tuo.
هان توه.
Who's this?
من هذا؟
I saw a pair of shoes at the entrance which I have never seen before.
رأيت زوجًا من الأحذية عند المدخل لم أره من قبل.
Did you have a friend staying over?
هل كان لديك صديق يقيم معك؟